RG 062:037, Town of Derby
Connecticut State Library
Town of Derby records
1805-1910
Connecticut State Library
Derby (Conn.)
11 cubic feet
Administrative and tax records for the town of Derby.
RG062_037
T000337
Historical Note
The town of Derby was named in May 1675 and incorporated on May 13, 1775. The City of Derby was incorporated on June 7, 1893. The town and city consolidated on June 7, 1893.
Scope and Content
Administrative and tax records for the town of Derby.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Derby -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Derby -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Derby -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Derby -- Registers
Places:
Derby (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
Use is restricted due to presence of mold from previous water damage and fragility of volumes. Please contact State Archives staff for assistance.
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1805-1910
  Use is restricted due to presence of mold from previous water damage and fragility of volumes.
  - Treasurer's account book, 1805-1849 (Box Box 1)
  - Record of earmarks and strays, 1812-1855 (Box Box 1)
  - Tax abstracts (Box Box 1)
    - 1822, 1824, 1825, 1826, 1827, 1828, 1829, 1830, 1835, 1837 (Box Box 1)
    - 1843, 1844, 1846, 1847, 1848 (Box Box 2)
    - 1853, 1854, 1857 (Box Box 3)
    - 1867, 1876, 1877, 1878, 1880, 1881, 1886 (Box Box 4)
    - 1881, 1882, 1883, 1884 (Box Box 5)
    - 1885, 1886, 1888 (Box Box 6)
    - 1889, 1890, 1891, 1892 (Box Box 7)
    - 1893, 1894, 1895 (Box Box 8)
    - 1896, 1897, 1898, 1899 (Box Box 9)
    - 1902, 1903, 1904 (Box Box 10)
    - 1905, 1906, 1907 (Box Box 11)
    - 1908, 1909, 1910 (Box Box 12)
    - Borough of Birmingham, 1882, 1883, 1885, 1886, 1887 (Box Box 13)
    - Borough of Birmingham, 1888, 1889, 1890, 1891, 1892 (Box Box 14)
    - Badly mildewed, unknown year, 1 volume (Box Box 15)
    - Unknown year, 1 volume (Box Box 15)